mygoogly.net 2009-07-01

# Privacy policy

Your privacy is important for us. This Policy applies to all pages under myGoogly. Here we let you know what information we collect when you use myGoogly. Why do we collect it, and how do we handle it. 

## Information what we collect and use

Why: All we do is to better serve the user’s experience. The cookies allow your browser to remember where you moved and placed your search box and the result list on your background. Collected data allows us to display your browser's free area for the background picture during every new page creation, you can trim it so it fits as good for you as possible. We also need to collect basic data to be able to build toplist, and to make our website searchable.

We offer services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information: URL, IP address, browser type and language, screen resolution, and the date and time of your request.

Cookies - When you visit myGoogly, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled (as detailed above).

Log information - When you use our services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

myGoogly processes personal information on our servers in the European Union. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services.

## Information sharing 

We don't share personal information with other companies or individuals outside of myGoogly. We do not rent, sell, or share any personal information about you.

If myGoogly becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. 

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data. 

## Information security 

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to people inside myGoogly, who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

## Data integrity 

We process personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate and current. 

## Changes to this policy 

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this website.
